french-property.com 2008-05-09

# Privacy Policy

|     | 

* * *

This website (the 'Website'), [www.french-property.com](http://www.french-property.com/) , is operated and maintained by IFP Ltd. In this policy 'we', 'us' and 'our' shall mean IFP Ltd. 

IFP Ltd. treat the privacy of your information seriously. We know that you care how information about you is used and shared and we appreciate your trust in us to do that carefully and sensibly. 

We have posted this policy to help you understand what information we are gathering, how we will use it and to demonstrate our commitment to your personal and financial privacy. By visiting the Website you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this privacy policy. We may change the content or services found on our Website at any time without notice and consequently our privacy policy may change at any time in the future. You agree to review this page regularly and your continued access to or use of the Website will mean that you agree to any changes.

* * *

## Security

We maintain strict security standards and procedures with a view to preventing unauthorised access to your information by anyone, including our employees. We use leading technologies such as (but not limited to) firewalls to protect the security of your information and our employees are bound by confidentiality agreements in relation to your information.

* * *

## How we use and disclose your personal information

We will ask you to provide us with certain up-to-date personal information about yourself in the provision of using our services. This will normally be collected as part of our sales process or during the registration process for some services. 

This information includes contact details such as name, contact information and payment details. If you represent a company or organisation we will also require the company name, company registration number and TVA number, where applicable. This personal information may change from time to time but can only be collected when you voluntarily give it to us. The information you agree to supply to us must be true, current, complete and accurate in all respects and you agree to notify us immediately of any changes to that information. Similarly, we strive to ensure the information we maintain about you is current, complete and accurate and we respond to requests to correct inaccurate information as soon as possible. 

We will use your information to facilitate and complete your transaction and, if necessary, may disclose your personal information to a party or provider to the transaction to do so. Your personal information may also be disclosed; if required to do so for legal reasons, to our agents and contractors in order to provide our services (on the understanding that information will be kept confidential), to any law enforcement agencies once we are satisfied as to the circumstances of the request, and/or to enforce our rights. If we sell or integrate our business with another we may pass your information to our advisers and those of prospective purchasers for this purpose (on the understanding that information will be kept confidential).

* * *

## Keeping you informed

We may use your contact and other details you provide through this website or when you register with us or from our records of our dealings with you, to obtain your views on our products and services, and to identify our products and services, and those of our strategic partners, which may be of interest to you. We may also share this information (but not your bank details) with these organisations so that we or they may contact you by letter, telephone, email and other reasonable electronic methods, with news and promotional information about property development and related services, such as estate agency, legal, financial advice and planning, and removals. By submitting your information through this website you agree that we may use your information in this way, unless you have indicated when you submit the information, that you do not agree to this, or you subsequently write requesting us to stop.

* * *

## Cookies

We may use 'cookies' on our website. A 'cookie' is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. They enable you to navigate around our Website and (where appropriate) enable us to tailor the content to fit your needs. They help us monitor the usage and activities on our website. They provide us with generic usage statistics to allow us to improve our Website and to provide you with information about our service that may interest you. Cookies are also used to help ensure the overall accuracy of the data collection and analysis processes described above. 

The web browsers of most computers are initially set up to accept cookies. However if you prefer, you can disable cookies through your Internet browser. Information about cookies and how to reject them can be found at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/ "All about cookies")

* * *

## International data transfers

If we need to transfer your information outside the European Union to countries whose data protection laws are not as extensive, we will keep control of the information or require anyone we pass it to, to treat it to European Union standards. Therefore, by browsing this Website and by communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal information in this way.

* * *

## Links to other websites

This privacy policy only applies to information relating to this website, so please read the privacy policies of other linked sites as we are not responsible for their content. Whilst we try to link only to websites which share our high standards and respect for privacy, we do not control, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

* * *

## Telephones

To ensure that we carry out your instructions accurately, to help us to continually improve our service and in the interests of security, our telephone lines can be digitally recorded and we may monitor these calls for training purposes or query resolution.

* * *

## Accessing your personal information

You have a right upon written request and payment of a fee, to have a copy of the personal information we hold about you.

* * *

## Contacting us

Please help us to keep your records up to date by informing us of any changes to your personal details. You can contact us in writing with any queries about how we handle your personal information at:

**Email:** [privacy@french-property.com](mailto:privacy@french-property.com)

**Post:** IFP Ltd.   
Unit 6 Victoria Business Park   
Short Street   
Southend-on-Sea   
Essex   
SS2 5BY   
UK

* * *

|     |   
---|---|---|---|---
